<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Archives on Sagindyk Urazayev</title>
    <link>http://people.eecs.ku.edu/~s383u895/archive/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Archives on Sagindyk Urazayev</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2018 16:20:21 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://people.eecs.ku.edu/~s383u895/archive/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Approximation of the limit of Divergent Series</title>
      <link>http://people.eecs.ku.edu/~s383u895/archive/cods/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2018 16:20:21 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://people.eecs.ku.edu/~s383u895/archive/cods/</guid>
      <description>Mathematics is the science of skilful operations, which are dealing with the logic of shape, quantity and rearrangement. Mathematics is using its core principles and rules to solve problems and get a reasonable answer. In my opinion, mathematics will soon run out of interesting theories if all new theories will formulate in terms of invented concept, which appear in axioms. This exploration is about finding finite values, limits for famous divergent series and later analytically extending Euler-Riemann&amp;rsquo;s zeta function to find a limit for any divergent series that can be formed by Euler- Riemann&amp;rsquo;s zeta function.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RSA: Encrypting, Decrypting, Hacking</title>
      <link>http://people.eecs.ku.edu/~s383u895/archive/rsa/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2018 20:41:53 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://people.eecs.ku.edu/~s383u895/archive/rsa/</guid>
      <description>By starting this Extended Essay with a lovely webcomic by Randall Munroe, one can guess that the “4096-BIT RSA” sounds like it is tough to crack. However, what is ”RSA” and how does it work that even a ”MILLION-DOLLAR CLUSTER” is not enough to crack it? The research question of this Extended Essay is - “Does R A provide secure data transmission and confidential certificate signatures?”
This Extended Essay will explore the history of RSA algorithm, the structure of the cryptographic technique, usage of it and ways to crack the algorithm.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>