<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Archives on Sagindyk Urazayev</title>
    <link>http://people.ku.edu/~s383u895/archive/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Archives on Sagindyk Urazayev</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 15:21:54 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://people.ku.edu/~s383u895/archive/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>http://people.ku.edu/~s383u895/archive/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 15:21:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://people.ku.edu/~s383u895/archive/resume/</guid>
      <description>Click here to open the full paper resume.pdf [Address:] 1515 Engel Road TEM 502 Phone: 917&amp;ndash;8451 [email:] sagindyk.urazayev@ku.edu [Github:] \@thecsw [Website:] people.ku.edu/~s383u895 [LinkedIn:] []()
Professional Skills **Computer Skills**: C, Python, emacs, git (Version Control System), [Linux], LaTeX, mySQL, Docker (Service Deployment, Containerization), Microsoft Word, Microsoft PowerPoint, Microsoft Excel, PostgreSQL, markdown, Org-Mode, Adobe Photoshop, html, bash, Perl, golang (Go), Java, C++, Microsoft Access, vim **Languages**: Russian, English, Kazakh, French  Education  [Current] Undergraduate Degree in [Computer Science] at **University of Kansas**, Lawrence, KS [May] 2018 International Baccalaureate Diploma Programme at **Quantum College**, Yerevan 2 years Thesis --- &amp;quot;RSA:Encrypting, Decrypting, Hacking&amp;quot; \| Advisor: Smbat Shahinyan [Final IB Score]: 37/45  Project Management Experience [Summer 2018 --- now] [Project Leader and Core Developer], *[Meme Investor bot](https://github.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Approximation of the limit of Divergent Series</title>
      <link>http://people.ku.edu/~s383u895/archive/cods/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2018 16:20:21 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://people.ku.edu/~s383u895/archive/cods/</guid>
      <description>Click here to open the full paper cods.pdf Abstract &amp;ldquo;Divergent series are an invention of the devil and it is shameful to base on them any demonstration whatsoever.&amp;rdquo; - @Abel &amp;ndash; N.H. Abel. 1826
Mathematics is the science of skilful operations, which are dealing with the logic of shape, quantity and rearrangement. Mathematics is using its core principles and rules to solve problems and get a reasonable answer. In my opinion, mathematics will soon run out of interesting theories if all new theories will formulate in terms of invented concept, which appear in axioms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RSA: Encrypting, Decrypting, Hacking</title>
      <link>http://people.ku.edu/~s383u895/archive/rsa/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2018 20:41:53 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://people.ku.edu/~s383u895/archive/rsa/</guid>
      <description>Click here to open the full paper rsa.pdf Introduction First time when I heard about RSA technique, was during the ITGS class in IB course. In ITGS Course Companion[@itgs] there is a chapter about Security and Secret Key Encryptions. As an example, the author included two cases of encryption: Symmetric Key Encryption or Single Key Encryption and Asymmetric key encryption, more known as Public Key Encryption.
During the lesson, the fact that a message can be encrypted by one key and only a second key can decrypt the message intrigued me.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>